Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Osta, born unable to harness mana,
was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's dark triad
also possess powers from the devils of the underworld
and use them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself
and from the support of his friends,
Osta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Xenon, one of the Spade Kingdom's dark triad,
attacked the Golden Dawn headquarters
with two of his underlings from the Dark Disciples.
What the hell do you think you're doing to my comrades?
Enraged at the sight of his friends being harmed,
Yuno defeated the two lesser foes.
Fifty-five percent.
Do you see what your problem is?
It isn't that you're weak.
I'm just that much better.
Just when Yuno's death seemed all but certain,
he was revived by the budding of Ygrusil,
the spell left behind by Captain Vangeance.
No!
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world
Yeah
We're gonna take you to the brand new world
To the brand new world
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world
Get your hands up, baby
We're gonna take you to the brand new world
Yeah
They drowned out
Get it on, get it on,始めよう
難航不落のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on, hold on
Now this time, fight for liberty
真実性 乗り込む常識をブレイ
逆境の先にある朝
Oh yeah
傾向に埋もらった人生の夢
Hands up
Shout it, shout it louder
Yes, do it, do it, start it
Never give up
限界を超えても
加速してexperience
We can't pay
Let's go home
Even myself
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground
想像性偽りのない自分の道
Yes
It's the ground
Hey yeah
Believe in myself
Believe in yourself
Hey yeah
Yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah
Yes
Yeah, yeah
Yeah yeah
Humanity
Is evil
Rage
Fear
Hatred
Hatred. Revenge. Destruction.
Evil is a human's nature.
And we have ceased to be amused by this mundane world.
Now then, I suppose I should be on my way.
What kind of human are you, Arcane Stage Mage Yame Tsukihiro?
This way!
I wonder how Loropechka and her pals have been doing lately.
I hope they've got lots of energy.
Then they'll be extra fun to crush!
It's so yummy!
The Heart Kingdom's got all kinds of delicious delicacies!
Oh, Charmy! You're so adorable!
My goodness! Those two really do make the perfect pair, don't they?
Cut it out, Loropechka!
She'll never stop eating if you keep spoiling her like that!
Look, she's about to pop!
It's no problem. Charmy will be super precious no matter how chubby she gets!
I couldn't agree more because a well-fed Charmy is a happy Charmy after all!
Did she seriously only come to the Heart Kingdom to find out what kind of snacks they had to offer?
Seems that way.
We need to focus. As it stands, we'll be fighting the Spade Kingdom any day now.
Fine by me! I'm ready to throw down whenever!
So am I. And we've taken over all of the towns surrounding the Spade Kingdom's border, so that should give us a decent advantage.
That's true, but we can't afford to get comfortable. Which is why Rill and Charlotte have made a trip back to the Clover Kingdom to participate in a Squad Captain's meeting.
I know, but I've got all this anticipation welling up inside, so it's hard to contain it.
Then come spar with me! Since I haven't gotten a chance to fight against you for real yet!
Yeah, that's a great idea! Let's see if Asta wants to join us too and then we can make it a three-way battle royale!
Asta's not here though.
What?!
Since we had a break from our training, he wanted to take a few gifts back. He and Finral went there together.
The battle is sure to be brutal, so it's smart to relax while we still have the chance.
Perhaps everyone should have something to eat!
Sorry, I've officially cleaned this pile of noms from myself.
On second thought, you'll have to locate food elsewhere.
I didn't realize it, but every single morsel of this belongs to Charmy.
That's why I said not to spoil her!
Are you ready, Undine?
Of course.
What's wrong, Lorpechka?
Spade is here.
It looks like six of them spread throughout the kingdom.
That was quick.
What about the Mana Zone barrier? They tore right through it?
Since Undine's clones are spread out, we were quickly able to notify the Spirit Guardians of their locations.
And they've taken defensive measures.
Even so, all six of these enemies are Stage Zero mages who possess a Devil's power.
This could prove difficult even for the Spirit Guardians.
I may ask for your help if things get too dire.
Lorpechka!
This intense magic.
It's Vanica, of the Dark Triad.
She's possessed by the Devil Megicula.
Megicula.
Great.
From the looks of it, I'd say we've killed about a hundred of them so far.
Lady Vanica, don't you think we should head to...
Not yet.
The more of Lorpechka's peasants we mow down, the more fired up she's bound to get.
That'll make this way more fun.
Yes, of course, me lady. As you...
Oh, yeah. Step on me more.
You pig.
The Neutral Zone. Between the Clover and Spade Kingdoms.
The Black Bull's hideout was placed here to serve as a first line of defense.
Hey, we're back from the Heart Kingdom! And we brought gifts!
You thought of us after being away for so long?
Well, aren't you a sweetie?
Good thing, too. Cause we're completely out of drinking snacks.
Um, hey! Nice to see you, Osta!
I sure wish I had a little more Maria around here.
Yeah, I can't really help you with that, Ghosh.
Uh, the Captain's meeting should be over with soon.
Guess I better go pick up Yami.
You're busy, huh, Finral?
We really appreciate everything you do, though.
Yeah, this job's exhausting. I'll be gone for a while.
It's a long trip, so I'm gonna make a bunch of stops.
Roger that.
Roger that. See you later!
Hey, how's Gordon doing? I bet he's been studying his curse magic like crazy, hasn't he?
Don't ask me. All I know about it is, I'm not going back there.
This is hard.
You can do it, son.
I believe in you.
Gordon, you really should eat.
That sandwich. It's exactly the same as the one you made for me when we had our first date.
Takes me back to the good old days.
Yes, when you were 18 and I was 17.
Our meeting was pure fate.
Papa, please tell me more about how you and Mama first met.
With pleasure.
I'd rather just focus on my studies.
So I guess Henry is still resting up?
Apparently his mana supply is low, since so many of us have been away from the hideout because of training and such.
And with Charmy gone, we don't have access to that mana recovery food she makes.
Yeah, Charmy's hooked on the snacks from the Heart Kingdom, so she probably won't be back for a while.
Nothing motivates her more than food, after all.
Oh, by the way, where's Magna?
Right, I forgot to mention. No sooner than he got back from his trip to the Heart Kingdom, he and Zora headed off somewhere else together.
I guess they get along, since they're both grumpy Gus's.
Is Henry awake?
I guess so. Is something wrong?
The hideout! It's floating!
So, Yami isn't home right now. In that case, perhaps you can entertain me while I wait for him. Shall we?
Spade's attacking us here?
He's the one who's making us float.
By himself?
Hmm.
Go, Rouge!
Meow!
Uh-oh.
Here we go!
Recombination magic! The Raging Black Pole!
If he wants a battle, then that's what I'll give him.
Large Reflect Refrain!
Mono Rocket Punch!
Insolence.
Gravity magic.
Presence of the Demon King.
What the hell kind of magic is that? Half of the force snapping like twigs!
And if it weren't for Rouge, then that would be us right now.
Despite being hit by my spell, you're still in one piece.
I'm guessing one of you has magic that influences natural laws.
I thought Yami was the only arcane stage here.
Excellent.
Your fight is with me!
My, aren't you a lively little nuisance?
Fair enough, then. I can spare you some attention.
Ahhhh!
Black Flash!
Gravity magic.
Presence of the Demon King.
He cancelled out my magic, then made his move.
Not half bad.
But I'm not done.
Ahhhh!
That magic may modify natural laws, but I didn't realize it could overturn death as well.
Let me guess, this cat belongs to you?
Stay behind Rouge, okay guys?
Forget them! Fight me!
Asta!
His magic's overwhelming.
And it's got such a wide range, too.
Not only can you manipulate the laws of nature, you're all so strikingly beautiful.
Dante of the Dark Triad. The pleasure is all mine.
The Dark Triad? Like the ones from Spade?
Those jerks are the reason our kingdom got wrapped up in this mess.
Now come.
You're going to be my woman.
You can't just take possession of someone like that!
I would love to see you try to stop me.
So you're the guy who's in charge, huh?!
What a delicious surprise.
I didn't know Clover had a devil possessed as well.
Black Divider!
Black METEORITE!
I can't hit him!
That anti-magic technique is made to track Mana.
So how did he dodge it?
And what do we do?
If he can sidestep that, then we'll keep attacking until he screws up.
How nice of him to come straight to our doorstep.
If we can win this fight, then the whole stupid mess will be over with.
I can't hit him!
That anti-magic technique is made to track Mana.
So how did he dodge it?
And what do we do?
If he can sidestep that, then we'll keep attacking until he screws up.
How nice of him to come straight to our doorstep.
If we can win this fight, then the whole stupid mess will be over with.
Hey, Asta!
Yeah, what's up?
New plan!
Look here!
Mirror Magic!
Mirror Brigade!
Mirror Meteorites!
This will scatter Asta's anti-magic.
And it moves incredibly fast, so if all goes well, he won't be able to evade it!
50%
You're kidding!
Did he just warp space?
What happened?
I'd like us to have a discussion.
True, we may have different ranks, but we're both devil-possessed.
I'm sure we can find some common ground.
We are nothing alike!
Nothing!
You're doing such terrible things to your own people!
How could I ever get along with you?
I don't understand all your melodramatic nonsense.
But if I disgust you, then that's quite the compliment.
So thanks for that.
Malice is an emotion that's unique to human beings.
It distinguishes us from all other animals.
But what am I saying?
I'm sure you're familiar.
Rage.
Hatred.
Revenge.
Destruction.
Malice has power.
Because whenever you let those feelings of malice take over, that's when you're at your most human.
After all, humanity's truest form is evil.
You're wrong.
I'll admit, I have bad thoughts every once in a while, too.
Sometimes they even give me more power to fight.
Thing is, I have a heart that's really strong, so I can control those feelings and use them to do good things instead.
That's what makes me human!
Is that so?
It seems that you're quite unique among those who are possessed by dev-
As long as I'm here, I won't let any of my friends die.
Naughty girl.
You're my woman now, remember?
And that means you can't use your power to help anyone.
Except for me.
Let's move to 60%.
This is awful.
I worked so hard to improve, to become stronger.
And he just undid everything in the blink of an eye.
My mana's depleted.
They can't operate the Black Bowl anymore.
I can't control my body!
This guy's got us pinned down!
We're sitting ducks!
I have to do something!
Gravity magic.
Evil God's pressure craft.
Have it your way.
Perhaps you'll be more driven if I appeal to your feelings.
No, wait!
Stop it now!
Stop!
Don't do it!
Oh no!
Oh my gosh!
I'm here with you.
My precious little boy.
There it is!
That's human nature!
Asta's attack was able to erase this guy's magic from the whole area.
Now then, let's find out what you can really do.
You'll never damage me with those techniques. You'll have to adjust your strategy.
I was hoping to chat with you a bit, but you appear to be lost inside yourself at the moment.
Perhaps you can tell me who that devil is, Lucifero.
I do not know. If any high-ranking devils are in the mortal realm now, it would probably be Zagred, who left the underworld. But I don't believe that's the case.
Erasing magic is a parlor trick. It must be the work of a being that possesses only a paltry amount of mana.
In other words, the boy is no match for us.
We are possessed by the mightiest of devils.
That's what makes us the Dark Triad.
The Dark Triad.
What's going on here?
on here. Something's off. It's like Asta's powers are going berserk. Still, we have to
rely on him. At this rate, Ghosh won't survive much longer. If only Nero were here to seal
his wounds. But even that might not be enough. Hang in there, Ghosh. Please don't leave us.
I'm so weak. I can't do anything. My transformation magic, it doesn't help at all. It's useless.
I'm impressed that you can still fight that hard. But I suppose I'll end this now.
Not giving up? How foolish. Anything you do is futile.
He predicted where I'd show up next. Interesting.
It seems you've left a small scratch.
You'll regret that.
Beautiful. Beautiful. Beautiful.
Well, you, you, now.
Let's sing it to you since i'm glad
So happy that you could spend time there.
How many times will you fly?
Beautiful
What kind of景色 can you see?
You and I will shine
That's why I'm always beside you
Never let go
My hand on my hand
Don't let go
I'd like to come anywhere
The world is so beautiful